Alexey Kozyurov

kozyurov.alexey@gmail.com

+79178822716

8

Казань

https://github.com/Leshe4ka



Short information -

I have been studying HTML, CSS, JS since April 2020. I was inspired to radically change my specialization by the success of my friends in the web development and disappointment in my previous job.

Skills —		
HTML5	CSS3	JavaScript
SCSS	Flexbox	БЭМ
Adobe Photoshop	Figma	Git
Webpack	Sass	Gulp

Experience -

codewars.com

5 kyu https://www.codewars.com/users/Leshe4ka

09/2020 - present

Freelance

Web-designer

09/2020 - present

• https://github.com/Leshe4ka

Two commercial projects have been completed in the new specialty:

- https://domik-vlesu.ru/
- https://podbor.neonero.ru/

Directorate for sports and social projects

Lead Manager of the Transport Department

10/2017 - 10/2019

Organization and holding of a number of Russian and world-class sports events in terms of providing transport services.

Education —

<u>Казанский (Приволжский)</u> федеральный университет, Казань

2015 - 2018

Казанский (Приволжский) Inst

федеральный университет, Казань

2011 - 2015

Institute of Management Economics and Finance. Specialty - Economics and Enterprise Management (Master)

Institute of Physics. Specialty - Radiophysics, Department of Quantum Electronics and Radio Spectroscopy (Bachelor's Degree)

About

A few words about me

My independent life began from the moment I entered the Kazan Federal University. During my studies at the Institute of Physics, I built and strengthened my analytical mindset. At the same time, I began to engage in social activities, which helped me become more responsible, acquired team management skills, knowledge of PCs (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Photoshop). Without hesitation, I began to apply the skills and knowledge acquired at the university in a new field-working as a tutor. There I learned to explain difficult things in simple language and teach other people. Thanks to a high-quality resume and study in a technical specialty, I got a job at the ANO Directorate of Sports and Social Projects. There I learned to plan my working day, react quickly to changes in the situation and make appropriate decisions. I got colossal experience in organizing transport services for Russian and global events.

Now, thanks to my high ability to learn, I tried on a new specialty - which I am incredibly happy about. This area allows me to realize my personal potential depending on external factors (be it politics, ecology or government, for example). The field of activity is really wide and has almost no boundaries, as well as a ceiling for growth.

I love traveling and am interested in music.